Report!
We've found the Dragon-Seeking Descendant.
Who are you?
I'm a descendant of the Dragon-Seeking Lineage.
I'll use the Dragon-Seeking Formula to help the Chief find the Tidal Tomb.
I also...
What was the next line again?
Where did you find this trash?
Calm down, Young Master.
Time is running out,
so we could only find someone around the same age.
You...
Forget it.
He'll have to do.
Let him shut the Wan and Mei families up first,
and help me become the Chief of the four families.
As for the real Dragon-Seeking Descendant...
Four days.
Find him within four days, no matter what.
Yes, sir.
Come back.
Memorize your lines properly.
You got it!
Li Xiao thinks he's so clever.
He only blew up the obvious path.
The real way out needs the right person to reveal it.
Where is he?
Wait for me!
It's a dead end.
What do we do?
Get back!
Hurry!
Here they come.
Zhang Tianyou.
Miss me?
You're the descendant of the
Zhang family's Dragon-Seeking Lineage?
That's right.
That would be me.
I will certainly assist the Chief
to find the Tidal Tomb from twenty years ago,
and help the Four Great Families
crack the tomb and quell the evil.
Then tell us how to find it.
Rumor has it that the tomb can move.
My Dragon-Seeking Lineage has a secret method,
the Dragon-Seeking Formula.
It reads the moving stars above
and the hidden earth veins below.
No matter how the Tidal Tomb drifts with the Dragon Qi,
it cannot escape my eyes.
Excellent.
Brother Wan, look.
This is destiny.
With the help of the Dragon-Seeking Descendant,
our grand plan is sure to succeed!
Great.
Since that's the case,
once Chun'er wakes up,
we will arrange your wedding immediately.
Brother Wan,
we must focus on the big picture.
How can a wedding compare to our grand plan?
The most urgent matter
is for this descendant
to deduce the Tidal Tomb's location at once.
And electing a Chief to take charge
is a matter of utmost urgency, Brother.
Then I'll leave it to you two.
Brother Wan,
I'll get to it right away.
Uncle Mei,
why won't you meet this Dragon-Seeking Descendant yourself?
Fenglin...
Some people are born to be sacrifices.
A man destined to die...
What's there to see?
Fenglin,
it seems before your father passed,
he really didn't tell you everything.
About that mess from twenty years ago,
it's far more complicated than you think.
Once we find that damn tomb again,
I'll tell you the whole truth.
But before that,
once that kid locates the Tidal Tomb,
stage an accident and make him disappear.
Make it clean.
Uncle Mei,
he's the Dragon-Seeking Descendant.
He's our key to cracking the tomb.
The key?
Fenglin,
when you see through an act,
there's no need to expose it.
We just need to see how things play out,
and take the right opportunity to...
clear the board.
Young Master.
Good thing Chief Leng was out there backing us up.
Otherwise, we'd both be
biting the dust right now.
How come you get a chicken leg?
And I don't?
You think this meal and our lives
came for free?
What do you mean?
To put it bluntly,
Chief Leng has been after my body for a long time.
I have to pay for our lives with it.
Well...
then you should eat more.
Or else...
Here, you eat it.
Forget it.
You eat it.
Remember to come save me!
Take care, Young Master!
Close the door.
Chief Leng.
Thanks for saving my life.
I prepared some wine to show my gratitude.
Have a seat.
A jug of wine isn't enough to repay a life debt.
Since you're here,
how do you plan to repay me?
You guessed it.
As for this thank-you gift...
only you are worthy of it.
What is this?
The personal gear of Sikong Zhaixing,
the Lock Saint of the Tang Dynasty.
It took me quite some effort to get my hands on it.
This thing is much more reliable than a man.
Zhang Tianyou, you...
You're quite a piece of work.
But do you think
Me saving you
was just for this?
I...
Of course not.
I, Zhang Tianyou, always repay my debts.
You saved me once,
so I owe you my life.
B-But...
I think my body is too weak.
I'm afraid I won't serve Chief Leng well.
Who wants your body?
Okay.
T-Then...
U-Um...
I'll be going now.
Get some early rest, Chief Leng.
This bastard.
More fun than those idiots thinking with their dicks.
Come in.
Young Master, we have a lead.
Based on intel from the Marshal's Mansion,
that person changed his name over a decade ago.
He's been hiding right under our noses.
Excellent.
Find him.
Dig him out even if you have to turn this place upside down.
Stall those old foxes outside first.
Once I truly secure the position of Chief,
I'll take my time dealing with them.
My father's greatest glory in this life
wasn't becoming the Marshal,
but having me.